Erol BicerNuclear Engineer



- +82-10-7497-0705
- ✓ erolbicer@live.com
- South Korea
- ## 1989 September 29
- www.erolbicer.com
- in LinkedIn
- R^G ResearchGate

LA	IN	G	U	AL	۶Ė	2

English • Turkish • Korean

/ST	-	v .	~	^	
/ 🕓 🗆	_ \	7/			

RELAP5 GOTHIC MARS-KS SPACE

CFD CODES

OpenFOAM

CAP

PROGRAMMING CODES

MATLAB FORTRAN C++

HTML/CSS

MISCELLANEOUS

DOS/UNIX
CATIA
Origin
ParaView
Mathcad

Git/GitHub

MS Office

PROFILE

Throughout my academic and professional career, I have focused on nuclear safety analyses at the plant, system, and component levels utilizing system safety analysis and computational fluid dynamics codes. I have experience with various baseload nuclear power plant technologies as well as small, and micro modular reactors.

EDUCATION

Nuclear Engineering, Ph.D., Seoul National University

2017 − present | Seoul, South Korea

Nuclear Power Plant Engineering, M.Sc., KINGS ☑ 2014 – 2016 | Ulsan, South Korea

Nuclear Energy Engineering, B.Sc., Hacettepe University

2008 – 2013 | Ankara, Turkey

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FNC Technology Co., Ltd. ☑

Associate Manager 2016 – present | Suwon, South Korea

Assistant Manager 2016 – 2019 | Suwon, South Korea

Bil-Plas Industry and Trade Co., Ltd., R&D Engineer

2013 − 2014 | Ankara, Turkey

CERTIFICATES

Modelling and Computation of Multiphase FlowsSwiss Federal Institute of Technology (ETH)

International Marketing, Business Knowledge and Intelligence Ankara Chamber of Commerce (ATO)

AWARDS

International Atomic Energy Agency Fellowship, IAEA

Full Academic Scholarship, KINGS

MAIN PROJECTS

[SMR] Small and Micro Modular Reactors Technology Analyses

[PCCS] Conceptual Design and Development of Passive Containment Cooling System for APR1400

[SMART] System-Integrated Modular Advanced Reactor Passive Containment Cooling System

[PGSFR] Prototype Gen-IV Sodium-Cooled Fast Reactor Condition Analysis

[PAFS] Passive Auxiliary Feedwater System Development

[ATLAS] Determination of ATLAS Heat Loss and Improvement of MARS Model

[EUR] APR1000 PAFS Standard Design Development and EUR Certification Support

More information can be found here **2**

PERSONAL VENTURES

Nuclear Industry Association of Turkey, Board of Directors $\ensuremath{\square}$

Turkish Chamber of Commerce in Korea, Co-Founder ☑

Hacettepe Rugby Club, Founder ☑